let questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "Where is Sanchi Stupa located?",
        answer: "Madhya Pradesh",
        options: [
            "Odisha",
            "Chhattisgarh",
            "Madhya Pradesh",
            "Uttar Pradesh"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "Where is Qutub Minar located?",
        answer: "Delhi",
        options: [
            "Delhi",
            "Haryana",
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Rajasthan"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "Where is Mysore Palace located?",
        answer: "Karnataka",
        options: [
            "Telangana",
            "Kerala",
            "Karnataka",
            "Tamil Nadu"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "Where is Fatehpur Sikri located?",
        answer: "Uttar Pradesh",
        options: [
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Haryana",
            "Delhi",
            "Madhya Pradesh"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "Where is India Gate located?",
        answer: "Delhi",
        options: [
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Punjab",
            "Haryana",
            "Delhi"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Where is Char Minar located?",
        answer: "Telangana",
        options: [
            "Maharashtra",
            "Andhra Pradesh",
            "Karnataka",
            "Telangana"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 7,
        question: "Where are Elephanta Caves located?",
        answer: "Maharashtra",
        options: [
            "Madhya Pradesh",
            "Maharashtra",
            "Karnataka",
            "Gujarat"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 8,
        question: "Where is Konark Sun Temple located?",
        answer: "Odisha",
        options: [
            "Chhattisgarh",
            "Jharkhand",
            "West Bengal",
            "Odisha"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 9,
        question: "Where is Hawa Mahal located?",
        answer: "Rajasthan",
        options: [
            "Gujarat",
            "Rajasthan",
            "Madhya Pradesh",
            "Punjab"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 10,
        question: "Where are Ajanta and Ellora Caves located?",
        answer: "Maharashtra",
        options: [
            "Gujarat",
            "Telangana",
            "Maharashtra",
            "Madhya Pradesh"
        ]
    }
]